-[MARI] How was it?
-I have this strange feeling.
I've never really felt this way
about Luca before.
I don't know
how to explain it properly.
-[MARI] What do you mean?
-I don't know,
I just have this
very warm feeling.
-Hmm, well, okay.
-[LARA] Huh?
I don't really get it, but
that's not important. I really
hope you find the true love
you've been searching for.
[hums]
Uh... Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I just tripped, it's all.
Are you still not used
to those legs?
[LARA] Oh, you never trip?
We're home!
Ah, Lara!
You're home late.
-We were worried.
-Yeah, call next time.
[♪ opening music begins]
[♪ opening music ends]
DOMINATE KINKI ! DOMINATE JAPAN!
ONE DAY UNTIL THE TOURNAMENT!
Listen up! Good work today,
everyone. Let's call it early so
-you can rest up for tomorrow.
-Yes, sir!
Mm, what is that?
Well, it's called a banner.
Mr. Makoto just taught me
about it. What do you think?
-Isn't it wonderful?
-Yeah, it's great.
[crowd cheering]
Wait, shouldn't you
be at Ondakan?
No, I took the day off today.
-Hmm.
-Huh?
-What are you watching?
-I'm studying the girl
-I'm going to fight tomorrow.
-[LARA] She looks really strong.
Maybe, but I'm still
going to win.
What will you do once you win?
Fight someone even stronger.
-And after that?
-Someone even stronger.
Oh.
-[LARA] Aren't you scared?
-Of what?
Hmm. Huh?
Lara?
[gasps] Lara?
I'm just fine.
Don't worry about it.
I just got a little sleepy.
[sighs]
-[honk]
-Huh.
SHIGA
[FEMALE] Nice to meet you,
Mari Otsu.
-I'm Lisa, Lara's older sister.
-[gasps]
[clock ticking]
[MARI] So you're really
Lara's older sister?
[LISA] I want you
to bring Lara back to me.
Okay then, why don't you just
ask Lara yourself?
[LISA] You don't understand.
Lara is our princess.
It is her duty to use her light
to save the mermaid race.
[MARI] Her light?
[LISA] Yes, the light
that only a princess
can obtain
through finding true love.
But if she can't find it,
it won't be long
before she vanishes into foam.
-Huh?
-[LISA] Lara took a potion
to become human. That potion
has an expiration date.
As soon as that date passes, she
will instantly turn into foam...
...and die.
H- huh?
How has Lara
been doing recently?
[gasps]
Hmm. That's what I thought.
This potion...
will help slow down the process.
It's the only thing
that can make her feel better.
But, unfortunately,
this is only a temporary fix.
If Lara wants to truly
save herself,
and her people,
she has to find true love.
I'm worried about her.
[MARI] Gon-chan!
-Hm. What is it?
-[MARI] Lara.
It's not true, right?
Is she going to turn into foam?
-Who told you that?
-[gasps]
LUCA
A ladybug got in the studio.
Do you know what a ladybug is?
No, I don't. Can you
show me one next time?
[footsteps approaching]
Hey, Mari.
Luca says he wants to come and
see your match tomorrow too.
I met your sister earlier today.
-Lisa?
-I didn't believe her at first,
but Gon-chan confirmed
that you're going to turn
into foam and disappear soon.
[gasps]
[MARI] Why did you keep this
from me? Why didn't you tell me
-about all this?
-[Lara gasps] I...
[sighs]
[thud]
Lara!
You need to understand, Lara is
terrified of the human world.
There is no hope of her
ever finding true love
while living in fear.
So I beg you, for me,
you need to bring Lara
back to us before it's too late.
-Lara.
-Mari.
Hey, are you feeling any better?
Sorry, I made you drink these
while you were asleep.
Your sister said
it would help you.
I feel a lot better, actually.
Thank you.
[LISA] But this is only
a temporary fix.
-So true love, huh?
-[LARA] Huh?
Do you think you'll find it?
Huh? What?
Of course I do.
I heard that a mermaid
has never fallen in love
with a human before.
-And yet...
-You're acting weird.
Don't worry about me.
Just wait and see.
Tomorrow everything will be
back to normal.
I think you should
go back to your sister.
-[LARA] But why?
-You can't go on like this.
What are you talking about?
I'm doing just fine.
-What did Lisa say to you?
-It doesn't matter.
Listen, I know I might be
causing a lot of trouble
for you all, but please
let me stay here.
Why?
Stop pretending you're okay.
-I'm not pretending.
-You're lying!
-I am not!
-Then why do you keep
looking at me like that?
Like you're scared?
[LARA] What's the big deal?
I'm not going anywhere.
Once I fold the futon and
change my clothes, I'm coming
to watch your match.
I'll work at Ondakan again,
and I'll even help
with the laundry.
And, and, and I'll get
even closer with Luca.
And then... someday I'll find
true love.
Yes, of course I'm scared!
I just...
I don't want you to die.
[car door opens]
NOTOGAWA ARENA
AUGUST 21ST TOURNAMENT DAY 1
[crowd cheering]
-Keep your hands up!
-Come on! Come on!
[♪ gentle music]
I WON'T BE ABLE TO
SEE YOU FOR A WHILE.
I can't believe she disappeared
and only left a note.
-Well, that was sudden.
-It really was.
She should have at least come
to cheer on Mari.
Can't you contact Lara?
No way.
She left her phone behind.
-Hmm?
-That lady who called you
is going to get in touch again,
right?
I don't know.
The potion seems to
have worked well.
Don't worry, the effects
should last for a while.
[LARA] Yeah, thank you.
Make yourself at home.
I want you to be comfortable.
AUGUST 22ND TOURNAMENT DAY 2
[bell rings]
[crowd cheering]
-Come on!
-You can do it!
And the winner by decision
is red corner Mari Otsu
from Tezumiya,
Shiga Prefecture.
[MAKOTO] Mari is amazing.
The finals are tomorrow.
Father and the others
are still asleep,
stuck in that dwelling that was
created by the accursed witch.
So you were with her? Is there
a reason you can't tell me?
Lara, don't worry.
I won't let her bother you
anymore.
-Lisa, you fool!
-Are you going to pester me
to bring her back
like you always do?
-Is that what you want me to do?
-No.
AUGUST 23RD TOURNAMENT
DAY 3: FINAL
[LISA] Since long ago
in ancient times,
the mermaid princesses have all
brought light into our world
through their deep love for the
ocean. There are no exceptions.
As long as that light shines,
father and the others will be
saved, and you too will be
spared from turning into foam.
You may stay
as long as you like.
I'm going to cheer my heart
out again today.
Yeah.
[panting]
[LUCA]
Huh? She's not here either?
-Then where is she?
-[MARI] I don't know.
What?
Have you tried calling her?
-I haven't.
-[LUCA] What?
This isn't like her.
Are you not worried?
[MARI] No, I'm not, because
Lara isn't coming back.
-[LUCA] Why?
-Just shut up already.
Did you guys have a fight or
something? It doesn't make
any sense.
How could you not know?
-Sorry.
-What?
Don't know. I don't know
anything about mermaids, okay?
Hey, what's wrong with you?
[grunts]
[♪ solemn music]
Humans are hideous,
despicable creatures.
[LARA] I've fallen in love.
For a mermaid and a human
to fall in love.
[LARA] For the first time,
I feel a kind of warmth.
You must go and find true love,
Lara.
[LARA] Who am I, really?
NOTOGAWA ARENA
The high school girls'
bantamweight final
is about to begin.
-What's that?
-Huh.
I can't hear a damn thing
with all this wind.
I'm actually on a boat heading
for home right about now.
Yeah.
Otsu, only those
who are prepared to fight
get to go up into the ring.
-Yes.
-Although I must say,
you don't look like you're up
for it at all right now.
You're wrong.
I'm gonna beat them up.
What are you saying to her?
I've got her fired up, don't I?
[phone vibrating]
-Hello?
- [LARA] Luca, can you hear me?
Hello, are you there?
-Luca, it's me, Lara.
-Lara? I can't hear you at all.
Hello, can you hear me?
LUCA AKIZUKI
[LUCA] Lara, where are you?
What are you doing?
I'm on a boat right now
with my sister.
-You're what?
-I said I'm on a boat.
Lara, Lara, are you okay?
-I was worried about you.
- [LARA] I'm sorry.
I might not be able to see you
guys ever again. I'm sorry.
You're going to have to
speak up. I'm sorry.
-I said this has to be goodbye.
-Lara?
[LARA] I don't understand
anything anymore.
[LARA] I... what's the point?
I just...
Next up, the high school girls'
bantamweight
final match.
In the red corner, we have...
[LARA]
Is Mari's match starting soon?
[LUCA] Oh, right.
I thought you were coming,
so I came over. Hold on.
Look at your screen. It looks
like it's just about to start.
Lara, aren't you coming?
What do you want to do?
Coming?
I just want to...
[bell rings]
I just want...
[gasps]
Lara!
[crowd cheering]
[LARA] I've decided I'm going
back to the human world.
[LISA] You don't
understand still?
It's impossible for you
to fall in love with a human.
[LARA] Maybe it is impossible.
I know that.
That's what scared me too.
But even though I was scared,
there was someone on the surface
who took my hand.
I met people
who made me feel at home,
even though I'm not from here.
They made me feel as if this is
where I'm supposed to be.
It's here on the above world
with these people
that I feel the light the most.
[grunting]
[LARA] So even though I may
be scared, I won't... give up!
[crowd cheering]
[grunting]
[MARI] No way.
This isn't happening.
OMI'S LIGHTNING
I don't wanna lose!
[crowd cheering]
[breathing]
No.
Mari!
[panting]
[whimpering]
No way.
There's no way I'm giving up!
What the...
Well, come on!
[grunting]
Mari!
[WOMAN] Mari is so strong.
Although I guess that's
how I raised her.
I have no doubt about it.
She's going to be strong enough
to make it on her own.
But still, even so,
there will come a time
when she finds someone
who will walk beside her.
-Oh.
-Yeah.
[snoring]
The both of you. You're going
to hear it when we get home.
And they're asleep.
They almost look like twins
when they're snoozing.
[MARI]
So what are you going to do now?
I'm going to keep
looking for love here.
-[MARI] So nothing new then?
-[LARA] That's right.
[LARA] But from now on, I'm not
going to be afraid anymore,
even if it's scary.
-[MARI] Hmm.
-[LARA] What do you mean "hmm"?
You're the one who asked.
-What are you going to do, Mari?
-What do you mean?
-From now on.
-Hmm.
Well, fight someone even
stronger, I guess.
-And then?
-Someone even stronger.
-Does it ever end?
-Never. It's a way of life.
-Pretty cool, right?
-I guess so.
Well, maybe I'll go pro.
-[LARA] Pro?
-If I become
the best in the world,
maybe even you'll understand.
-Hmm.
-What's that supposed to mean?
Okay, if you become the best in
the world, I'll bake you a cake.
-Uh.
-I can even make custard,
-your favorite.
-[sighs]
-[MARI] Oh yeah, you mean it?
-[LARA] Of course I do.
[MARI] You've got yourself
a deal.
I need you to promise me though.
[LARA] Yeah, I promise.
TO BE CONTINUED
[♪ closing music begins]
Translation: Sachiko Takahashi
Timing: Andy Ellis
Editing and Typesetting:
Ashley Barboza
Quality Control: Riley Dalton
Translation Check:
Sriram Gurunathan
[♪ closing music ends]